

Masoud Hesami

Date of birth: 28/12/2000

Nationality: Iranian

Gender: Male

CONTACT

Sari, Iran

Masoodhesami79@gmail.co m

(+98) 9901405737

LinkedIn: https://

linkedin.com/in/masoud-

<u>hesami</u>

Other: https://github.com/

masoodhesami

ABOUT ME

Front-end developer with more than 1 year experience working with React.js & Next.js, interested in developing websites, math lessons, problem solving discussions and learning more about technologies world. I'm a regular person in doing things and it's important for me to write organized code. I am usually an active person and i do my work creatively.

WORK EXPERIENCE

01/07/2021 - 11/12/2021 - Sari, Iran

Frontend Developer

APANCO

Redesign and develop academy website & academy admin panel Small team leadership experience in a React.js contest and doing Ui & Ux design for projects, with Adobe XD.

website features:

Courses page, Buy course, Like & dislike course, Authorized user, Blog Teachers page, FAQ page, Search box & comment, Admin panel etc.

Technologies & Frameworks:

React js, Node js, Material Ui, Bootstrap, Core Ui etc.

10/12/2020 - 10/06/2021 - Sari, Iran

Intern Web Developer

APANCO

learning Html, Css, Javascript, Sass, Jquery, Ajax, React.js etc.

Doing low level tasks for different websites.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

23/09/2019 - CURRENT - Babol, Iran

Computer engineering

Babol Noshirvani University of Technology (BNUT)

DIGITAL SKILLS

Front-end

HTML5/CSS, Javascript / jQuery / Sass / React js / React-Redux / Redux / Typescript / Axios / Restful APIs / POSTMAN / Next.js **Design**

Adobe Photoshop / Adobe Xd / Figma

Ui frameworks

Bootstap / Material Ui / Tailwind CSS

Source controller

Git / Github / Gitlab

Back-end

Node.Js / Express.JS / Mongodb / MongoDB/Mongoose

Algorithms

Python / Cpp

PROJECTS

Academy-project

https://github.com/masoodhesami/Academy-project Sepehr Academy Project with React.js

Academy-admin-panel

https://github.com/masoodhesami/Academy-admin-panel Sepehr Academy admin panel with CoreUi

Personal-site

https://github.com/masoodhesami/Personal-site My personal website design & develop by me

React-socketio-chat-app

https://github.com/masoodhesami/React-socketio-chat-app React.js chat application with express & socketio

HONOURS AND AWARDS

16/04/2022

FUNDAMENTALS OF PYTHON PROGRAMMING AND ALGORITHMIC

THINKING - Quera

https://masoodhesami.ir/certificates/fundamentals.jpg

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Persian

OTHER LANGUAGE(S):

English

Listening	Reading	Spoken	Spoken	Writing
B1	B2	production	interaction	B1
		B1	A2	